fromnaturewithlove.com 2019-04-25

# Your Privacy - FNWL

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase with us at [http://www.fromnaturewithlove.com](http://www.fromnaturewithlove.com/) ("our website"). 

## The Personal Information That We Collect

When you visit our website, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse our website, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the website. We refer to this automatically-collected information as _Device Information._

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

_Cookies_ are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

_Log files_ track actions occurring on our website, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. They do not include your name, email address, address or any other personally identifying information.

_Web beacons, tags_ and _pixels_ are electronic files used to record information about how you browse our website.

When you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through our website, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as _Order Information._

When we talk about "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

## How We Use Your Personal Information

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through our website (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).

Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud
  * When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, we may also provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our website (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with our website, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

## Sharing Your Personal Information

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use authorize.net to securely process credit card orders. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use our website. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. 

As described above, we may use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative's ("NAI") educational page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work>. 

You can opt out of targeted advertising directly at these sites:

Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>

Google: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>

Bing: <https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads>

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance's opt-out portal at: <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

## Do Not Track

Please note that we do not alter our Site's data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser. 

## Your Rights

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through our website), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to the United States.

## Data Retention

When you place an order through our website, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

## Mailing List Subscriptions

Our mailing list requires subscribers to double-opt in. You are welcome to unsubscribe at any time by using the Unsubscribe Link on our Mailing List page.

## Changes

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

## Contact Us

For more information about our privacy practices, please contact us.

|  |   
---|---|---
